cambridgeassessment.org.uk 2016-05-07

# Privacy Settings | Cambridge Assessment

###  Privacy settings 

#### Use of cookies by Cambridge Assessment

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. These are used in order to make websites work more efficiently, as well as to provide useful information about how websites are being accessed and used.

Here is some information about the cookies we use on the Cambridge Assessment website and why.

ASP.NET SessionId | ASP.NET_SessionId | This cookie is created by our website and stores a users session ID. The cookie does not contain any personal data and expires at the end of the users session - when the browser is closed.  
---|---|---  
Cookie consent | cc_analytics   
cc_media   
cc_social | These cookies are used to inform users that cookies are used on our website and to allow users to select and save their preferences. A further cookie is used to ensure a users choices are remembered across the website.  
Google Analytics | _utma   
_utmb   
_utmc   
_utmv   
_utmz | These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors access and use our site. This is used to monitor performance, for reporting, and for providing data that will influence the improvements made to the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of people visiting the site, their gender and age, how many pages they looked at and what pages they visited.  
Google Adwords Remarketing | __gads | We use Google Adwords remarketing to improve our advertising. For example, to improve reporting on advertising campaign performance, to avoid showing ads the user has already seen or to enable us to display advertising that is more relevant to users. Third party vendors including Google use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Cambridge English website. Any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy. 

If you’d like to set your preferences for how Google advertises to you, please go to the [Google Ad Preferences](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads?hl=en-GB&sig=ACi0TCg4fCAz34nE7_X63UgnD5zYFwciPfIMHMkv4UE9s-guY46tpOBYOJ4bv4a3gM7yMU7oyyNR14sRQLV3pvNHfz4EUmutMDcaBYiygpaaIi2VcZjIlryCeCPel0hOxlPYRVXN5JjbhDrw44xLSkhz1JyPkZL6oj9ZwqGR4tJhDrGTuSjL50o "Google Ad preferences") page.  
  
JWPlayer | __jwpusr | This cookie is used by the video and podcast player on our website to store a users viewing preferences.  
Survey Monkey | Various | These cookies are created by Survey Monkey which we use for occasional website surveys.  
Wufoo forms | Various | These cookies are created by Wufoo which we use for our web forms.  
Website Survey | JulyCASurvey | This cookie is used to prevent our website survey from displaying if it has already been closed or completed by a user. The cookie expires after one year and does not contain any personal data.  
Crazy Egg Heatmap | is_returning | This cookie is used to determine whether a user is a new visitor to our website. The cookie expires after five years and does not contain any personal data.
